♪♪
♪ Words like violence ♪
♪ Break the silence ♪
♪ Come crashing in ♪
♪ Into my little world ♪
♪ Painful to me ♪
♪ Pierce right through me ♪
♪ Can't you understand ♪
♪ Oh, my little girl ♪
♪ All I ever wanted ♪
♪ All I ever needed
is here in my arms ♪
♪ Words are very unnecessary ♪
♪ They can only do harm ♪
♪ Vows are spoken ♪
♪ To be broken ♪
♪ Feelings are intense ♪
♪ Words are trivial ♪
♪ Pleasures remain ♪
♪ So does the pain ♪
♪ Words are meaningless ♪
♪ And forgettable ♪
♪ All I ever wanted ♪
♪ All I ever needed
is here in my arms ♪
♪ Words are very unnecessary ♪
♪ They can only do harm ♪
♪ All I ever wanted ♪
♪ All I ever needed
is here in my arms ♪
♪ Words are very unnecessary ♪
♪ They can only do harm ♪
♪ All I ever wanted ♪
♪ All I ever needed
is here in my arms ♪
♪ Words are very unnecessary ♪
♪ They can only do harm ♪
♪♪
♪ Enjoy the silence ♪